William Safire Papers
William Safire Papers
- Subject files
  - European Rapid Reaction Force (ERRF) (Box 229)
  - European Union (EU) constitution (Box 229)
  - Ewing, W. Hickman (Box 229)
  - Excavating (Box 229)
  - Executive privilege (Box 229)
  - Exner, Judith (Box 229)
  - Export controls (Box 229)
  - Facts of life materials, sex education; 3 folders (Box 490)
  - Farragut, David G. (Box 229)
  - Farrakhan, Louis (Box 229)
  - Fazio, Vic (Box 229)
  - FBI (Federal Bureau of Investigation) (Box 229)
    See also Subject files Berlin - CIA - FBI; Freedom of Information Act (FOIA): FBI.
  - FBI justice (Box 229)
  - FBI / White House travel office (Box 229)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission), 2 folders (Box 229)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission), 11 folders (Box 230)
  - FCC (Federal Communications Commission), 3 folders (Box 231)
  - Fed Ex (Box 231)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Robert Pitofsky (Box 231)
  - Feingold, Russell (Box 231)
  - Fifth Amendment (Box 231)
  - Filegate, 3 folders (Box 231)
  - Financial derivatives (Box 231)
  - Finding (Box 231)
  - Finkelstein, Jerry (Box 231)
  - Finkelstein, Jerry, National Law Journal (Oversize 6)
  - Fischer, David C. (Box 231)
  - Flag burning (Box 231)
  - Flat tax (Box 231)
  - Florida election, 2000 (Box 231)
  - Ford, Gerald (Box 490)
  - Foreign ministers (Box 231)
  - Foster, Vincent
    - [General], 6 folders (Box 232)
    - Citizen's Independent Report (Box 232)
  - Foxman, Abraham (Box 232)
  - France, 4 folders (Box 232)
  - Franco-German proposal (Box 232)
  - Franking privilege, 3 folders (Box 233)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)
    See also Subject files Deaver, Michael: Freedom of Information Act; Miller, Judith: Freedom of Information Act.
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 233)
    - CIA (Box 233)
    - Defense Department (Box 233)
    - Department of Agriculture (USDA) (Box 233)
    - Department of Justice, Ed Rogers (Box 233)
    - Eavesdropping (Box 233)
    - FBI (Box 233)
    - Letter generator (Box 233)
    - Personal (Box 233)
    - Requests (Box 234)
    - Secret Service (Box 234)
    - State Department (Box 234)
    - State Department, John Kelly (Box 234)
    - USDA (Department of Agriculture) (Box 234)
    - USIA (US Information Agency) (Box 234)
  - Freeh, Louis J. (Box 234)
  - French connection (Box 234)
  - Full Disclosure movie (Box 234)
  - Furmark, Roy (Box 234)
  - Gambling
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 234)
    - [General], 8 folders (Box 235)
    - [General], 13 folders (Box 236)
    - [General], 7 folders (Box 237)
    - California (Box 237)
    - College (Box 237)
    - Indiana casino, 2 folders (Box 238)
    - Indians (Box 238)
    - Pequot Indians (Box 238)
  - Garbage (Box 238)
  - Garment, Leonard (Box 238)
  - Gates, Robert (Box 238)
  - Gati, Toby (Box 238)
  - Gay marriage (Box 238)
  - Gender gap (Box 238)
  - Georgia, Republic of (Box 238)
  - Gephardt, Richard (Box 238)
  - Germ warfare, 2 folders (Box 238)
  - Germany, 4 folders (Box 238)
  - Ghazi, Sheikh [Ghazi Mashal Ajil al-Yawer] (Box 239)
  - Gillray cartoonist (Box 239)
  - Gingrich, Newt, ethics (Box 239)
  - Glaspie, April, 3 folders (Box 239)
  - Global crossing (Box 239)
  - Global warming (Box 239)
  - God (Box 239)
  - God's world (Box 239)
  - Golan Heights (Box 239)
  - Goldsmith, James (Box 239)
  - Goodwin, Richard (Box 239)
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail, Summit (spring 1990) (Box 239)
  - Gore, Al
    See also Subject files Reno, Janet: Gore, Al.
    - [General] (Box 239)
    - Buddhists (Box 239)
    - Gilbert Merritt (Box 239)
  - Government telephone audit (Box 239)
  - Graham, Billy (Box 239)
  - Graham, Martha (Box 239)
  - Grand jury reform (Box 240)
  - Grand Union TV show (Box 490)
  - Gray, C. Boyden, 2 folders (Box 240)
  - Greater Middle East Initiative (Box 240)
  - Greenberg, Maurice R., critic (Box 240)
  - Greenspan, Alan (Box 240)
  - Gregg, Judd, 2 folders (Box 240)
  - Gridiron Club, 7 folders (Box 240)
  - Grigoryants, Sergei (Box 241)
  - Gryphon Editions Advisory Board (Box 241)
  - Gusinsky, Vladimir, 2 folders (Box 241)
  - Haas, Richard (Box 241)
  - Haiti (Box 241)
  - Halevi [Halevy], Ephraim (Box 241)
  - Halloween memorandum (Box 241)
  - Hamas (Box 241)
  - Hammerson, Sylvie (Box 241)
  - Hammond, Paul (Box 241)
  - Hannon, Kemp (Box 241)
  - Harassment (Box 241)
    See also Subject file Sexual harassment.
  - Harry Walker Agency (Box 241)
  - Hart-Rudman Commission, 2 folders (Box 241)
  - Hate crime legislation (Box 241)
  - Hate crime legislation, 2 folders (Box 242)
  - Hay-on-Wye booksellers (Box 242)
  - Hazony, Yoram (Box 242)
  - Headhunters (Box 242)
  - Health care (Box 242)
  - Health care reform (Box 242)
  - Healy, Bernadine (Box 242)
  - Hechler, Ken, 2 folders (Box 242)
  - Hedge funds, 2 folders (Box 242)
  - Helms, Jesse (Box 242)
  - Heymann, Philip (Box 242)
  - Hill (Box 242)
  - Hoagland, Jim (Box 242)
  - Home improvement (Box 242)
  - Homeland Security Day After Plan (Box 242)
  - Homeless (Box 242)
  - Hong Kong (Box 242)
  - Hong Kong (Box 490)
  - Housing sweeps (Box 242)
  - Hoaxes (Box 242)
  - Hsia, Maria, 2 folders (Box 242)
  - Huang, John
    See also Subject files Lippo: Huang, John.
    - [General], 4 folders (Box 243)
    - Chao, Elaine (Box 243)
    - China (Box 243)
  - Hubbel, Webster (Box 243)
    See also Subject files Lippo: Hubbel, Webster.
  - Hudson Shipping Company (Box 243)
  - Hungary (Box 243)
    See also Subject file Travel: Hungary.
  - Hurricane scale ranges (Box 243)
  - Hussein, Saddam (Box 243)
  - Hutton, E. F. (Box 243)
  - Iacocca, Lee (Box 243)
  - IBM, 2 folders (Box 243)
  - Ideas (Box 244)
  - Identity theft (Box 244)
    See also Subject file Privacy: Identity theft.
  - Immigration (Box 244)
  - Impact, Inc. (Box 490)
  - Impeachment (Box 244)
  - Inaugural address, second (Box 244)
  - Independent counsel (Box 244)
  - Independent counsel hearing (Box 244)
  - India (Box 244)
    See also Subject file Deaver, Michael: India.
  - India, embassy of (Box 244)
  - Indonesia (Box 244)
  - Inflation (Box 244)
  - Inman, Bobby Ray
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 244)
    - Cartoons (Box 244)
    - Mail (Box 245)
    - Massie, Robert K. (Box 245)
    - Nice letters (Box 245)
    - Pollard, Jonathan (Box 245)
  - Inouye, Daniel K. (Box 245)
  - Inslaw, Inc. (Box 245)
  - Inspector Generals (Box 245)
  - Intelligence, 2 folders (Box 245)
  - Internal Revenue Service (IRS), See IRS.
  - International Chamber of Commerce (ICC) (Box 245)
  - International Criminal Court (ICC) (Box 245)
  - International Herald Tribune (Oversize 6)
    See also Subject file Singapore: International Herald Tribune.
  - International Republican Institute (Box 245)
  - Internet, See Privacy: Internet; Singapore: Internet.
  - Investment advisers (Box 245)
  - Invitations, speaking (Box 245)
  - Iran
    See also Subject files Bahá'ís, Iran; Bosnia: Iran; Contras; Israel: Iran; Rappaport, Bruce: Iran/Contra reactions.
    - [General] (Box 245)
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 246)
    - Contra, 4 folders (Box 246)
    - Iraq (Box 246)
    - Ledeen, Michael A. (Box 246)
    - Missiles (Box 246)
  - Iraq
    See also Subject files Atta, Mohammad; Barzani, Masoud; Hussein, Saddam; Iran: Iraq; Kissinger, Henry: Iraq.
    - [General] (Box 246)
    - [General], 8 folders (Box 247)
    - [General], 5 folders (Box 247)
    - Safire essays (Box 248)
  - Iraqi Media Network (IMN) (Box 248)
  - IRS (Internal Revenue Service) (Box 248)
  - Israel
    See also Subject files American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC); Clinton, Bill: Israel; Golan Heights; Jerusalem; Jewish people and Israel; Travel: Israel; Turkey: Israel.
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 248)
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 249)
    - Airborne Early Warning and Control (AEW&C) (Box 249)
    - Carter Middle East policy (Box 249)
    - China (Box 249)
    - China, spying (Box 249)
    - Condemn (Box 249)
    - Democrats (Box 249)
    - Geneva Convention (Box 249)
    - Iran (Box 249)
    - Madrid Peace Conference (Box 249)
    - Security fence (Box 249)
    - Spy story (Box 249)
    - State Department (Box 249)
  - Israeli Secret Service book ban (Box 249)
  - Israeli settlements in Arab territories (Box 249)
  - Iwo Jima (Box 249)
  - J - general (Box 250)
  - Jackson, Jesse (Box 250)
  - Jail to the Chief (Box 250)
  - James Jr., Fob [Forrest Hood] (Box 250)
  - Jamison, Dr. Kay Redfield (Box 250)
  - Janklow, Morton L.
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 250)
    - Doubleday language books (Box 250)
    - Janklow and Traum (Box 250)
    - Janklow and Traum, 2 folders (Box 251)
    - Norton Book of Speeches (Box 251)
  - Japan (Box 251)
  - Jefferson, Thomas (Box 251)
  - Jerusalem, 2 folders (Box 251)
  - Jewish civilization (Box 251)
  - Jewish people and Israel (Box 251)
  - Jewish People Policy Planning Institute, 2 folders (Box 251)
  - Jewish People Policy Planning Institute, 2 folders (Box 252)
  - Jewish reaction to Safire, 3 folders (Box 252)
  - Jewish vote (Box 252)
  - Jews
    See also Subject files American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC); Anti-semitism; Ethiopian Jews; Israel.
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 252)
    - [General] (Box 253)
    - Politics (Box 253)
  - Jintao, Hu (Box 253)
  - Job (Box 253)
  - John King Books (Box 253)
  - Johnson, Norma Holloway (Box 253)
  - Johnson, Samuel (Box 253)
  - Joint economic committee (Box 253)
  - Joint inquiry (Box 253)
  - Jones, Dr. Stephen (Box 253)
  - Jones, Paula (Box 253)
  - Jordan (Box 253)
  - Jordan, Vernon (Box 253)
  - Journalism (Box 253)
  - Judge for sale (Box 253)
  - Judges as plumbers, 2 folders (Box 253)
  - Judicial watch (Box 253)
  - Judson Welliver Society
    - [General], 6 folders (Box 254)
    - Correspondence (Box 254)
    - Dinner parties, 6 folders (Box 254)
    - Founders (Box 255)
    - Lists (Box 255)
    - Members (Box 255)
    - Members (Box 256)
    - Thank you notes (Box 256)
  - Junk bonds (Box 256)
  - Jury duty (Box 256)
  - Justice (Box 256)
  - Karr, Mary (Box 256)
    See also Subject file Syracuse University: Karr, Mary.
  - Kashmir (Box 256)
  - Kerensky, Alexander (Box 256)
  - Kerry, John (Box 256)
  - Kevorkian, Jack (Box 256)
  - Keyes, Alan (Box 256)
  - KGB, 3 folders (Box 256)
  - Kievan Rus' Christians (Box 256)
  - Kimmitt, Robert (Box 256)
  - Kirkland, Irena (Box 256)
  - Kirkland, Lane (Box 256)
  - Kissinger, Henry
    - [General] (Box 256)
    - Iraq (Box 256)
  - Klaus, Vaclav (Box 256)
  - Kneejerks summer vacation essays (Box 256)
  - Kol Shalom Synagogue (Box 256)
  - Korda, Michael, fixes (Box 257)
  - Korea, See Deaver, Michael: Korea.
  - Kovach, Bill (Box 257)
  - Kozyrev, Andrei
    - [General] (Box 257)
    - Yavlinsky, Grigory (Box 257)
      See also Subject file Yavlinsky, Grigory.
  - Kristol, Bill (Box 257)
  - Krock, Arthur (Box 257)
  - Kudos (Box 257)
  - Kuhn, Robert Lawrence, 2 folders (Box 257)
  - Kurds
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 257)
    - [General], 7 folders (Box 257)
    - [General], 7 folders (Box 257)
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 258)
    - CIA (Box 260)
    - Columnists (Box 260)
    - White House (Box 260)
  - Kuwait (Box 260)
  - La Bella, Charles G. (Box 260)
  - Laffer, Arthur B. (Box 260)
  - Lagrangian codes (Box 260)
  - Lake, Tony (Box 260)
  - Lance, Bert (Box 260)
  - Language (Box 260)
  - Language books (Box 260)
  - Language of Journalism, 4 folders (Box 260)
  - Language publicity (Box 261)
  - Lapid, Tommy (Box 261)
  - Lasers (Box 261)
  - Latvia, 4 folders (Box 261)
    See also Subject files Russia: Latvia; Soviet Union: Latvia.
  - Laufer, Stephen (Box 261)
  - Law of the sea (Box 261)
  - Law of the sea convention (Box 261)
  - Layoffs (Box 261)
  - Leading Authorities, Inc. (Box 261)
  - Leaks (Box 261)
  - Lebanon (Box 261)
  - Lebed, Aleksandr, 2 folders (Box 262)
  - Lecture
    - [General] (Box 262)
    - Agencies (Box 262)
    - Ethics (Box 262)
  - Legal department memos (Box 262)
  - Lehrer, Jim (Box 262)
  - Lenzner, Terry (Box 262)
  - Leroy, Warner (Box 262)
  - Levitas, Mike (Box 262)
  - Lewis, Anthony (Box 262)
    See also Subject file Pulitzer Prize: Lewis, Anthony.
  - Lewis, Flora (Box 262)
  - Lewis, John L. (Box 262)
  - Libel (Box 262)
    See also Subject file Deaver, Michael: Libel.
  - Libertarians (Box 262)
  - Library of Congress
    - [General] (Box 262)
    - Personal papers (Box 262)
    - Photoduplication requests (Box 262)
  - Lie detector (Box 262)
    See also Polygraphs.
  - Lie detector, 6 folders (Box 263)
  - Limbaugh, Rush
    - [General] (Box 263)
    - Safire interview (Box 263)
  - Limited buy-outs (Box 263)
  - Limousine services (Box 263)
  - Lincoln, Abraham
    - [General] (Box 263)
    - Oates, Stephen, 2 folders (Box 264)
  - Lindsay, Bruce, 3 folders (Box 264)
  - Lippo
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 264)
    - Asian connections (Box 264)
    - Bank (Box 264)
    - Burton, Dan (Box 264)
    - Giroir, C.J. (Box 264)
    - House Oversight Committee (Box 264)
    - Huang, John (Box 264)
    - Hubbell, Webster (Box 264)
    - Justice (Box 265)
    - Kantor, Mickey (Box 265)
    - Notes (Box 265)
    - Riady, Mochtar (Box 265)
    - Road map (Box 265)
  - Livingstone, Craig, 2 folders (Box 265)
  - Locke, John (Box 265)
  - Lofgren, William (Box 265)
  - Logan Act (Box 265)
  - London (Box 265)
    See also Subject files Book dealers, London; Travel: Budapest, Prague, Paris, London; Travel: London (numerous dates).
  - London book shops (Box 265)
    See also Subject files Book dealers, London.
  - Lottery (Box 265)
  - Loyalty
    - [General] (Box 265)
    - Letters, 2 folders (Box 265)
  - Luchese - Cols (Box 490)
  - Madison, James (Box 265)
  - Mafia, Russia (Box 265)
  - Mahoney Institute of Neurological Sciences (Box 265)
  - Mahoney, David J.
    - [General] (Box 265)
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 266)
    - Book (Box 266)
    - Resume (Box 266)
  - Malaysia (Box 266)
  - Malek, Fred (Box 266)
  - Management terms (Box 490)
  - Mankiewicz, Frank (Box 266)
  - MARC train schedules (Box 266)
  - Marriage (Box 266)
    See also Subject file Gay marriage.
  - Marron, Donald B. (Box 266)
  - Marshall, Andrew, 2 folders (Box 266)
  - Marstellar, Burson (Box 266)
  - Maugein, Patrick, 2 folders (Box 266)
  - McCain, John
    - [General] (Box 266)
    - Speeches (Box 267)
  - Mayoralty campaign (Box 490)
  - McCall's magazine (Box 267)
  - McCawley, James (Box 267)
  - McCrary, Tex
    - [General], 6 folders (Box 267)
    - 80th birthday party (Box 267)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 268)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. and Ronald Reagan (Box 268)
    - Falkenburg, Jinx (Box 268)
    - Legal (Box 490)
    - Letters (Box 268)
    - Memos (Box 490)
    - Powell, Colin (Box 268)
    - Tex McCrary Inc. (Box 490)
    - "Tex: What A Life!": John Reagan McCrary and Charles Kelly (Oversize 6)
    - World War II (Box 268)
  - McFarlane, Robert (Box 268)
  - McGraw-Hill (Box 268)
  - McLaughlin, Ann, 2 folders (Box 268)
  - Media (Box 268)
    See also Subject files Accuracy in media; Iraqi Media Network (IMN); Soviet Union: Media.
  - Medina, Kate (Box 268)
  - Melville, Herman (Box 490)
  - Meese, Ed (Box 268)
  - Meet the Press (Box 268)
    See also Media files Videocassettes: Guest appearances for Safire's appearances on the show.
  - Meet the Press, 6 folders (Box 269)
  - Meet the Press, 7 folders (Box 270)
  - Memoirs
    - [General] (Box 270)
    - Early New York Times (Box 271)
    - King Jr., Martin Luther (Box 271)
  - Menschel, Robert (Box 271)
  - Mergers (Box 271)
  - Miami maps (Box 271)
  - Miller, Judith
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 271)
    - Articles by Miller, Judith (Box 271)
    - Articles by Safire, William (Box 271)
    - Book excerpts (Box 271)
    - Correspondence (Box 271)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 3 folders (Box 272)
    - Government memoranda (Box 272)
    - Miller standard for confidential waivers (Box 272)
    - Press clippings, 6 folders (Box 272)
    - Press clippings, 4 folders (Box 273)
    - Release (Box 273)
    - Research notes (Box 273)
    - Shield Law, 3 folders (Box 273)
    - Shield Law (Box 274)
    - Testimonies, 2 folders (Box 274)
    - Testimonies by Safire, 2 folders (Box 274)
  - Missile defense, 3 folders (Box 274)
  - Missile defense (Box 275)
  - Mistakes (Box 275)
  - Mitchell, John (Box 275)
  - Montauk (Box 275)
  - Moon landing (Box 275)
  - Morgaine, Sylvain (Box 275)
  - Morgenthau, Robert (Box 275)
  - Morris, Dick (Box 275)
  - Mosbacher, Robert (Box 275)
  - Moscow
    See also Subject files Soviet Union: Moscow; Summits: Moscow; Travel: Moscow (two dates).
    - [General] (Box 275)
    - [General] (Box 490)
    - Trade (Box 275)
  - Moscow Pictures (Box 490)
  - Most favored nation (Box 275)
  - Mount Alto, 2 folders (Box 275)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick (Box 275)
  - Mozambique (Box 275)
  - Mubarak, Hosni (Box 275)
  - Mulroney, Brian (Box 275)
  - Mulroney, Brian (Box 276)
  - Munich Conference on Security Policy, 2 folders (Box 276)
  - Muravchik, Joshua (Box 276)
  - Murdoch, Rupert (Box 276)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MOMA)
    - [General] (Box 276)
    - Photography book introduction (Box 276)
  - Musicals (Box 276)
  - Muslims
    - [General] (Box 276)
    - Michigan (Box 276)
    - Voters (Box 276)
  - Mutual and Balanced Force Reduction (MBFR) (Box 276)
  - Nader, Ralph (Box 277)
  - National Aerospace Plane (NASP) (Box 277)
  - National Comment magazine (Box 277)
  - National Economic Commission (Box 277)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 277)
  - National Security Decision Directive 84 (NSDD 84), 2 folders (Box 277)
  - Nationalism (Box 277)
  - NATO, 2 folders (Box 277)
    See also Subject file Russia: NATO.
  - NATO, 3 folders (Box 278)
  - Natural born (Box 278)
  - Naturalization (Box 278)
  - Naturalized Citizens Amendment (Box 278)
  - Nazi art treasures (Box 278)
  - Nemtsov, Boris (Box 278)
  - Neoconservatism (Box 278)
  - Neoliberal (Box 278)
  - Netanyahu, Benjamin (Box 278)
    See also Bibi notes.
  - Neuroethics speech (Box 278)
  - Nevins, Jane (Box 278)
  - New boy network (Box 278)
  - New cities (Box 278)
  - New freedom, Mary Lawrence (Box 278)
  - New liberal ideas, 2 folders (Box 279)
  - New socialism (Box 279)
  - New York Close Up
    - A-B (Box 279)
    - C-D (Box 279)
    - E-F (Box 279)
    - G-H (Box 279)
    - I-J (Box 279)
    - K-L (Box 279)
    - M-N (Box 279)
    - O-Q (Box 279)
    - R-S (Box 279)
    - T-Z (Box 280)
  - New York City (Box 491)
  - New York guide (Box 520)
  - New York Philharmonic (Box 280)
  - New York Public Library account (Box 280)
  - New York Times
    - [General] (Box 280)
    - Benefits (Oversize 6)
    - Digital (Box 280)
    - Employment, See Employment, New York Times.
    - Merchandise (Box 280)
    - Names, addresses (Box 481)
    - Op-ed columns (Box 280)
    - Party (Box 280)
    - Pension, See Subject file Pension, New York Times.
    - Staff (Box 280)
    - Wall Street Journal (Box 280)
  - New Yorker (Box 280)
  - Newman, Ralph Geoffrey (Box 280)
  - Nexis, 4 folders (Box 280)
  - Nightline transcripts (Box 280)
  - Nixon Center for Peace and Freedom (Box 280)
  - Nixon, Richard
    See also Subject file Singapore: Nixon.
    - [General] (Box 280)
    - [General], 8 folders (Box 281)
    - [General], 4 folders (Box 282)
    - ACLU (Box 282)
    - Alumni (Box 282)
    - Campaign poster (Map-case 108)
    - Conference transcripts (Box 282)
    - Daughters (Box 282)
    - Economics, 2 folders (Box 282)
    - Family (Box 282)
    - Haldeman, H.R. (Box 282)
    - Interview (Box 282)
    - Never Trust a Local (Oversize 6)
    - New despotism (Box 282)
    - New Nixon (Box 282)
    - Notes (Box 282)
    - People (Box 283)
    - Phone calls (Box 283)
    - Pictures (Box 283)
    - Speech book (Box 283)
    - Stamps (Box 283)
    - Tapes (Box 283)
  - Nofziger, Lyn (Box 283)
    See also Michael Deaver: Nofziger, Lyn.
  - Nolan, Beth (Box 283)
  - Noonan, Peggy (Box 283)
  - Nordex (Box 283)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), See NATO.
  - North Korea (Box 283)
  - Norton, Gale A. (Box 283)
  - Nosenko, Yuri (Box 283)
  - Nuclear Arms (Box 283)
  - Nussbaum, Bernard W. (Box 283)
  - Oates, Stephen, See also Subject file Lincoln, Abraham: Oates, Stephen.
  - Odom, William E. (Box 283)
  - Okrent, Daniel (Box 283)
  - Office
    - Cleaners of leather furniture (Box 283)
    - Furniture (Box 283)
    - New (Box 283)
    - Pool (Box 283)
    - Stationery (Box 284)
    - Supplies, fax machine (Box 284)
    - Supplies, printer (Box 284)
    - Temporary help (Box 284)
  - Oil (Box 284)
  - Oil for Food (Box 284)
    See also Subject file United Nations: Oil for Food.
  - Oil imports, 5 folders (Box 284)
  - Olsen, Ted (Box 284)
  - Oman (Box 284)
  - Op-ed diplomacy (Box 284)
  - Ostrow, Stuart (Box 284)
  - Ostrow, Stuart (Box 285)
  - Overseas contacts (Box 285)
  - Overseas Press Club (Box 491)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation (OPIC) (Box 285)
  - Packwood, Bob
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 285)
    - Diaries (Box 285)
  - Pakistan (Box 285)
  - Palestine Liberation Organization (PLO) (Box 285)
  - Palladino, Jack (Box 285)
  - Panama, Mike Harari (Box 285)
  - Papal encyclical (Box 285)
  - Pardons (Box 285)
    See also Subject files Clemency; Clinton, Bill: Pardons.
  - Party (Box 285)
  - Patent reform (Box 285)
  - Patriot act (Box 285)
  - Patriot missile (Box 285)
  - PBS (Box 285)
  - PEN American Center (Box 285)
  - Pennies, 2 folders (Box 286)
  - Penny (Box 286)
  - Pension, New York Times (Box 286)
  - Perjury (Box 286)
    See also Deaver, Michael: Perjury.
  - Perle, Richard, 2 folders (Box 286)
  - Perorations (Box 286)
  - Perot, Ross, 3 folders (Box 286)
  - Persian Gulf (Box 286)
  - Persian Gulf War, conservative split (Box 286)
  - Personal newspaper clippings (Box 491)
  - Personnel (Box 286)
  - Pet insurance (Box 286)
  - Philippines (Box 286)
  - Photographs (Box 286)
  - Pilchuck School (Box 286)
  - Pinker, Steve (Box 286)
  - Piperline Blast (Box 286)
  - Pitofsky, Robert, See Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Robert Pitofsky.
  - Plastic bags (Box 286)
  - Plaza Hotel (Box 286)
  - PLO, See Palestine Liberation Organization.
  - Pocket calendar (Box 286)
  - Poindexter, John M., 3 folders (Box 287)
  - Poland (Box 287)
    See also Subject file Travel: Poland.
  - Polisario Front (Box 287)
  - Political memorabilia (Box 287)
  - Pollard, Jonathan Jay, 3 folders (Box 287)
  - Polls
    - [General] (Box 287)
    - Cell phones (Box 287)
  - Pollsters (Box 287)
  - Polly Lobby, 2 folders (Box 288)
  - Polygamy (Box 288)
  - Polygraphs
    See also Lie detectors.
    - [General], 7 folders (Box 288)
    - Legislation (Box 288)
    - Legislation (Box 289)
    - Letters and columns, 2 folders (Box 289)
  - Polympics (Box 289)
  - Pope (Box 289)
  - Powell, Colin (Box 289)
    See also Subject file McCrary, Tex: Powell, Colin.
  - Power backup (Box 289)
  - Prague, 2 folders (Box 289)
  - Predictions (Box 289)
  - President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board ("Piffiab") (Box 289)
  - Presidential campaign hotline (Box 289)
  - Presidential health (Box 289)
  - Presidents (Box 289)
  - Price control (Box 289)
  - Priggé, Alan (Box 289)
  - Primakov, Yevgeny, 2 folders (Box 290)
  - Primary reform (Box 290)
  - Primary rules (Box 290)
  - Princess Diana, See Diana, Princess of Wales.
  - Princz, Hugo (Box 290)
  - Printing (Box 290)
  - Prism (Box 290)
  - Privacy
    See also Subject file Snooping.
    - [General], 3 folders (Box 290)
    - [General], 6 folders (Box 291)
    - [General], 8 folders (Box 292)
    - Advocates (Box 293)
    - Age of Consent (Box 293)
    - American Bar Association (ABA) conference (Box 293)
    - Banks (Box 293)
    - Bush, George W. (Box 293)
    - Business, 2 folders (Box 293)
    - Congress, 3 folders (Box 293)
    - Consent (Box 294)
    - Consumer (Box 294)